<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio Projects on ANGGA FUADY</title>
    <link>https://fuady.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio Projects on ANGGA FUADY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fuady.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tableau: World Life Expectancy Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/post/life_expectancy_dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/post/life_expectancy_dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Highlights Objectives Shows female and male life expectancy for each country over time Compute the average life expectancy for each continent Outcome World life expectancy Dashboard Overview Life expectancy is the key metric for assessing population health. It tells us the average age of death in a population.
Life expectancy has increased rapidly since the Age of Enlightenment. In the early 19th century, life expectancy started to increase in the early industrialized countries while it stayed low in the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: Car insurance fraud predictions</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/post/insurance_fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/post/insurance_fraud/</guid>
      <description>Highlights Objectives Investigate variables with the highest fraud Fit prediction model for fraud prediction Determine the influential variable for prediction Outcome Car incidents mostly happens in the afternoon at 17.00 Insured with Mercedes, Ford, and Audi often commit fraud Two most influential variable for insurance car fraud prediction are vehicle claim and incident severity Prediction using decision tree model gives the largest accuracy (83%) Data set The data can be downloaded is here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python: Shot on goal visualization</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/post/shot_on_goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/post/shot_on_goal/</guid>
      <description>Highlights Objectives Web scraping of shot on goal in single match Show pitch visualization including shots coordinate Shows timing match Outcome Visualization of shot on goal location and its Outcome Visualization of timing match (minutes vs cumulative expected goal) In this project, we are interested in replication of shot on goal visualization and timing chart of EPL match between Liverpool and Wolverhampton Wanderers on May 22, 2022. Liverpool wins 3-1 against the opponent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau: Offline Retail Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/post/walmart_dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/post/walmart_dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Highlights Objectives Shows the profit trends over time Shows the average profit per state Shows the average profit per region over time Outcome The average profit for all states is USD 181.18 South Dakota has the highest average profit, while Montana has the lowest. Only in Central region, the average profit is higher in 2015 compare to in 2012 In 4th quarter of 2012, East region has the highest average profit Retail Dashboard Visualization process In this project, I use Tableau for building the dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R: Exploratory data analysis EPL in FIFA20</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/post/fifa20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/post/fifa20/</guid>
      <description>Highlights Objectives Overview of average age, value, overall skills and potential for each club Most valuable player for each position Visualize player comparison Outcome Man. City is the club with the highest value and Potential Wolves has the youngest squad in this season Chelsea leads the highest average overall player skills Kevin de Bruyne is the most valuable player of the season De Bruyne outperform Pogba in the attacking, movement and mentality Alisson has a higher positioning and kicking value compare to De Gea This post will explore data of players and clubs in the premier league season 2019/2020 from FIFA20 video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Angga Fuady. I studied mathematics in Bachelor and Master degree (ITB, Indonesia) and continuing a PhD in the field of statistics (LUMC, The Netherlands). Having a solid analytical background and curiosity give me the energy to find the &amp;lsquo;aha&amp;rsquo; moment and valuable insight from the data. To extract some insights, I used mostly visualization as well as machine learning technique. For my daily work, I prefer to use R and Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://fuady.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuady.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn | Github | Email</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
